<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>brewscheme</title>
    <description>Making it easier for you to generate the data visualizations you want from Stata less verbose, easier to reproduce, and more flexible for inclusion in production environments.</description>
    <link>https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 08:43:58 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 08:43:58 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bug fixes and minor feature additions prior to version 1.0</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;using-symbol-types&quot;&gt;Using symbol types&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a way to remind myself to get around to adding this, I submitted a &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/wbuchanan/brewscheme/issues/18&quot;&gt;feature/enhancement request&lt;/a&gt; for handling symbol types in scheme files.  There is now a fix for this on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/wbuchanan/brewscheme/tree/symbols&quot;&gt;symbols branch&lt;/a&gt; in brewscheme.ado.  There is an example of how the feature can be used on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/brewtheme/&quot;&gt;brewtheme&lt;/a&gt; page and with a few more tests I anticipate this making it into the release.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;other-updates&quot;&gt;Other Updates&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few users have had issues with the installation process.  I’ve tried adding a fix to for this particular issue (caused when there is no personal subdirectory on the ADOPATH) in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/wbuchanan/brewscheme/tree/personaldirectory&quot;&gt;personaldirectory branch&lt;/a&gt;.  If you have issues getting things installed please submit an issue using these instructions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;// Start logging all the output
log using brewschemeIssueLog.txt, text replace

// Print information about your system/Stata
about

// Print the operating system
di `&quot;`c(os)&#39;&quot;&#39;

// Print the system directories
sysdir

// Get the package ID for any existing installations of brewscheme
ado, find(brewscheme)

// Remove any installations that currently exist
// In the syntax below the [] is required and the # should be the number displayed 
// from the command above
ado uninstall [#]

// You may need to repeat the second step a few times.  If there are different installations on your machine
// Once the package has been completely uninstalled:

// Install the current version
net inst brewscheme, from(&quot;http://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme&quot;) rep

// Set the preference for the traceback depth to decend three levels into the program call
set tracedepth 3

// Turn on tracing
set trace on

// Compile the mata libraries
libbrewscheme

// Build out the color database
brewcolordb, ref

// try your commands here


// Close the log file 
log c _all
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That should provide a fair amount of information that I can use to trace issues and replicate problems that you may have.  In some cases, I may not have access to the operating system you use, but there generally shouldn’t be too many issues caused by the OS at this point.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 00:10:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/update/2015/12/11/minor-features-and-bug-fixes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/update/2015/12/11/minor-features-and-bug-fixes.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting ready for version 1 release</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;new-feature-addition&quot;&gt;New feature addition&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;brewproof&lt;/code&gt; prefix command has finally been added to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/wbuchanan/brewscheme&quot;&gt;brewscheme&lt;/a&gt; collection of programs.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/brewproof/&quot;&gt;brewproof&lt;/a&gt; is a command that allows users to quickly and easily create proofs of their data visualizations that simulate the appearance of the graph to individuals with achromatopsia (complete color vision loss), protanopia (red color vision impairment), deuteranopia (green color vision impairment), and tritanopia (blue color vision impairment) without having to modify their existing syntax beyond the addition of &lt;code&gt;brewproof, scheme(brewscheme generated scheme name):&lt;/code&gt; to the start of the command.  For additional information, examples, and to see the output of the command, please visit the &lt;a href=&quot;https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/brewproof/&quot;&gt;brewproof&lt;/a&gt; page.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;other-newsupdates&quot;&gt;Other news/updates&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The addition of the &lt;code&gt;brewproof&lt;/code&gt; command marks the end of development for the v 1.0.0 release.  No new features will be added prior to the release of this first major version.  However, some of the plans for the next release include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Providing option for brewscheme/brewtheme to generate CSS file(s)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;More comprehensive color translations (e.g., translating across color spaces, etc…)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Color distance estimation (e.g., to help users pick the most contrasting color given an input)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 22:50:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/update/2015/12/01/getting-ready-for-version-1-release.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/update/2015/12/01/getting-ready-for-version-1-release.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New addition to the brewscheme family</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;brewscheme&lt;/code&gt; now includes new Mata classes/methods to simulate the color that would be perceived by individuals with varying types of color sightedness impairments.  Additionally, similar to &lt;a href=&quot;https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/brewviewer/&quot;&gt;brewviewer&lt;/a&gt; there is also an analogous program available to show how the simulated color values would appear called &lt;a href=&quot;https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/brewcbsim/&quot;&gt;brewcbsim&lt;/a&gt;.  Future development will exapand the options of both brewcbview (e.g., to handle multiple color tuples and display them in a single graph), brewviewer (e.g., to show a preview of specific palette combinations under varying forms of color sightedness impairment), to add the simulated colors to lookup tables used by &lt;a href=&quot;https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/brewscheme/&quot;&gt;brewscheme&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/brewtheme/&quot;&gt;brewtheme&lt;/a&gt;, and to create a proofer for Stata graphs that would show how they would appear under different forms of color sight impairment.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, comments, requests, and collaborators are always welcome.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 23:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/update/2015/11/24/new-addition-to-brewscheme-family.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/update/2015/11/24/new-addition-to-brewscheme-family.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A new homepage for BREWSCHEME</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I decided to learn a bit more about creating GitHub Pages using Jekyll to make the site a bit more useful.  You’ll still &lt;br /&gt;
find the same content that was previously located in the README, but it should be easier to navigate back and forth between &lt;br /&gt;
the subroutines in the package now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 23:30:31 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/update/2015/11/17/new-site.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/update/2015/11/17/new-site.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
