<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>brewscheme</title>
    <description>Making it easier for you to generate the data visualizations you want from Stata less verbose, easier to reproduce, and more flexible for inclusion in production environments.</description>
    <link>https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 03:10:20 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 03:10:20 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>New addition to the brewscheme family</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;brewscheme&lt;/code&gt; now includes new Mata classes/methods to simulate the color that would be perceived by individuals with varying types of color sightedness impairments.  Additionally, similar to &lt;a href=&quot;https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/brewviewer/&quot;&gt;brewviewer&lt;/a&gt; there is also an analogous program available to show how the simulated color values would appear called &lt;a href=&quot;https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/brewcbsim/&quot;&gt;brewcbsim&lt;/a&gt;.  Future development will exapand the options of both brewcbview (e.g., to handle multiple color tuples and display them in a single graph), brewviewer (e.g., to show a preview of specific palette combinations under varying forms of color sightedness impairment), to add the simulated colors to lookup tables used by &lt;a href=&quot;https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/brewscheme/&quot;&gt;brewscheme&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/brewtheme/&quot;&gt;brewtheme&lt;/a&gt;, and to create a proofer for Stata graphs that would show how they would appear under different forms of color sight impairment.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, comments, requests, and collaborators are always welcome.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 23:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/update/2015/11/24/new-addition-to-brewscheme-family.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/update/2015/11/24/new-addition-to-brewscheme-family.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A new homepage for BREWSCHEME</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I decided to learn a bit more about creating GitHub Pages using Jekyll to make the site a bit more useful.  You’ll still &lt;br /&gt;
find the same content that was previously located in the README, but it should be easier to navigate back and forth between &lt;br /&gt;
the subroutines in the package now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 23:30:31 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/update/2015/11/17/new-site.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://wbuchanan.github.io/brewscheme/update/2015/11/17/new-site.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
